2023/08/22
Created Calc-Ultra

2024/03/03

Added colored output (Rich)

2024/03/06

Added double integral option to InteCalc

2024/03/07

Patch factorial, gamma, polygamma, and erf function graphing bugs (Scipy)

Added graphing style settings

2024/03/10

Edited syntax

Edited graphing for factorial function.

2024/03/20

Created AlgCalc, the algebra calculator. Calc-Ultra now supports vectors, matrices and equations!

2024/03/27

Patched bugs of AlgCalc (equation solver)

2024/04/14

Added progress bars (Rich), increased tolerance of input (ln <-> log, e <-> E, a <-> arc), simplified code, increased tolerance of input for implicit differentiation.

2024/04/20

Added function parameter specifications in code to improve readability, and fixed input tolerance bugs.

